Finding Aid for the Augustus F. Hawkins papers LSC.1642
UCLA Library Special Collections
- District Office Files, ca. 1934, 1948, 1953, 1963-90; (Contained in 39 Boxes)
  - Subject Files, 1963-75
    - Hearings
      - Job Opportunities for Minorities, April 1970. (Box 93)
      - Anti-Poverty, March 1965. (Box 93)
    - Highways, Century Freeway Proposal. (Box 93)
    - Housing and Urban Development
      - Ardmore Project. (Box 93)
      - California Fair Housing Law. (Box 93)
      - Hoover Redevelopment Project. (Box 93)
      - Community Development
        - IMPAC ([South Central] Improvement Action Council), Ujima Village, (4) Pico-Union Neighborhood Council (PUNC)., 1967-72 (Box 93)
      - General Correspondence. (Box 93)
      - Huntington Park, Housing Analysis. (Box 93)
      - Model Cities, (6)., 1968-73 (Box 93)
      - Newsclippings. (Box 93)
    - Industry
      - Industrial Development Corporation (IDC). (Box 94)
      - Southern Pacific Industrial Development Plan. (Box 94)
    - Jokes and Sayings. (Box 94)
    - Juvenile Delinquency. (Box 94)
    - Labor
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous. (Box 94)
      - Full Employment Task Force. (Box 94)
      - The New Manpower Act, December 1973. (Box 94)
      - Newsclippings. (Box 94)
      - On-the-Job Training Programs. (Box 94)
      - Opportunities Industrialization Center, Incorporated. (Box 94)
      - Westminister Neighborhood Association. (Box 94)
    - Legislation
      - Emergency Relief Act. (Box 94)
      - Emergency School Assistance Act, H.R. 13915, 1972. (Box 94)
      - Higher Education Act of Analysis., 1972 (Box 94)
      - Miscellaneous. (Box 94)
    - Library of Congress. (Box 94)
    - NAACP, General Correspondence. (Box 94)
    - Natural Resources, National Forests, Clearcutting. (Box 94)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity
      - General. (Box 94)
      - 1971-72. (Box 94)
      - Child Day Care Centers. (Box 94)
      - Compton-Willowbrook Enterprise Community Action Project. (Box 94)
      - Coordinating Council on Economic Development and Employment (CCEDE). (Box 94)
      - Economic Youth Opportunities Agency (EYOA). (Box 94)
      - EYOA, Teen Post. (Box 94)
      - Head Start, Parents' Improvement Council Project. (Box 94)
      - Head Start Programs. (Box 94)
      - Head Start Complaints. (Box 94)
      - Huntington Park Multi-Purpose Service Center. (Box 94)
      - Job Corps Center for Women. (Box 94)
      - Neighborhood Adult Participation Project (NAPP). (Box 94)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps. (Box 94)
      - Parent and Child Centers. (Box 94)
      - Summer Youth Opportunity Programs. (Box 94)
      - Unity Charity Society. (Box 94)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Project. (Box 94)
      - Watts Labor Community Action Committee/ Council. (Box 94)
      - Watts Neighborhood Law Office Advisory Council. (Box 94)
      - Watts-Willowbrook-Compton Improvement Association. (Box 94)
    - Political Affairs
      - Campaigns, Bradley Campaign. (Box 94)
      - Campaigns. (Box 94)
      - Democratic Clubs and California Democratic Party. (Box 94)
      - Democratic National Committee. (Box 94)
      - Elections. (Box 94)
      - Congressman Hawkins, Election/ Reelection and Endorsement Correspondence. (Box 94)
      - National Black Political Convention,, Gary, Indiana., March 1972 (Box 94)
      - Negro Elected Officials. (Box 94)
      - General Correspondence. (Box 95)
      - Newsclippings. (Box 95)
      - Negro Political Action Association of California. (Box 95)
      - Operation Gear-In Voter Registration. (Box 95)
      - Voting Records. (Box 95)
    - Pollution, Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box 95)
    - Population. (Box 95)
    - Postal Service
      - General. (Box 95)
      - Mt. Wilson, California, Commemorative Stamp. (Box 95)
      - Huntington Park Post Office. (Box 95)
      - Paramount Post Office. (Box 95)
      - South Gate Post Office. (Box 95)
    - Prisons, State
      - General Correspondence. (Box 95)
      - Chino, California. (Box 95)
      - Chino, Randy Shepphard Fund for Kidney Transplants. (Box 95)
    - Public Activities
      - Appointments. (Box 95)
      - Condolences. (Box 95)
      - Congratulations. (Box 95)
      - Congressional Record Inserts, General. (Box 95)
      - Congressional Record Inserts, (5)., 1968-71, 1973 (Box 95)
      - Criticisms, Personal. (Box 95)
      - Donations Refused. (Box 95)
      - Greetings. (Box 95)
      - Honors. (Box 95)
      - Invitation. (Box 95)
      - Recommendations. (Box 95)
      - Charles Knox Personal. (Box 96)
      - Requests for Bills. (Box 96)
      - Memberships. (Box 96)
      - Personal Business Transactions. (Box 96)
      - Personal Contributions. (Box 96)
      - Personal Friends, Correspondence. (Box 96)
      - Requests, Miscellaneous. (Box 96)
      - Deborah Roberson. (Box 96)
      - Awards, Given and Received. (Box 96)
      - Biographical Material. (Box 96)
      - Courtesy Thank Yous. (Box 96)
      - Gratuitous Thank Yous. (Box 96)
    - Questionnaire Responses, Results, March 1973. (Box 96)
    - Race Relations
      - Black-Brown Committee. (Box 96)
      - General Correspondence and Newclippings. (Box 96)
    - State Department
      - Congressman Hawkins Incident re UNESCO Conference in Paris. (Box 96)
      - General Correspondence. (Box 96)
    - Taxes
      - Revenue Sharing. (Box 96)
      - Revenue and Taxation. (Box 96)
    - Transportation
      - General Correspondence. (Box 96)
      - Newsclippings. (Box 96)
    - Publicity
      - General. (Box 96)
        - Address, before the Thomas Jefferson High School graduating class, Los Angeles, California, 1967 (Box 96)
      - Correspondence. (Box 96)
      - Notes for Radio, TV Tapes. (Box 96)
      - Reaction to Press. (Box 96)
      - Speech Material. (Box 96)
      - Speech, The Mobility of the Non-English Speaking Adult Population, January 1968. (Box 96)
      - Speech Material. (Box 96)
    - State Affairs, Los Angeles Community Improvement
      - Watts Arts Festival. (Box 96)
      - Watts Tower. (Box 96)
      - Wrigley Field. (Box 96)
      - S. Central Area Welfare Planning Council Report, What Watts Citizens Want. (Box 96)
    - Veterans
      - Brownsville Raid, Mr. Warfield's Funeral. (Box 96)
      - Brownsville Incident Correspondence. (Box 96)
      - Brownsville Incident Newsclippings. (Box 96)
      - National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students, re Vietnam-Era Returning Servicemen and Women. (Box 96)
      - Returning Vietnam Veterans Statistics. (Box 96)
      - Vietnam War Newsclippings. (Box 96)
    - Welfare, Social
      - Programs for Aged. (Box 96)
      - Food Stamps. (Box 96)
      - HEW, Office of Education. (Box 96)
      - Newsclippings and Corres. (Box 96)
      - HEW, Public Health Service. (Box 96)
      - HEW, Social Security Administration. (Box 96)
      - VISTA (Volunteers in Service to America). (Box 96)
    - White House
      - Enemies List. (Box 96)
      - Background Information, White House Staff and President Nixon's Campaign Organizations. (Box 96)
      - General. (Box 96)
  - Subject Files, 1973
    - Inter-Office Correspondence. (Box 49)
    - Pension Reform Bill. (Box 49)
    - Telegrams. (Box 49)
  - Subject Files, 1975
    - Projects. (Box 71)
    - Public Relations (4). (Box 71)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 71)
    - Referrals (2). (Box 71)
    - Requests (2). (Box 71)
    - Staff. (Box 71)
    - Schools, 29th District. (Box 71)
    - Schools, Miscellaneous Staff. (Box 71)
    - State Democratic Committee. (Box 71)
    - SubCommittee on Equal Opportunities. (Box 71)
    - Telegrams. (Box 71)
    - Thank You. (Box 71)
  - Subject Files, 1976
    - A. (Box 71)
    - County Democratic Central Committee. (Box 71)
    - Hawkins Family Foundation. (Box 71)
    - IMPAC, (South Central] Improvement Action Council. (Box 71)
    - Legislation (2). (Box 72)
    - Los Angeles County CETA. (Box 72)
    - Neighborhood Adult Participation Project, South Central Manpower Training Center. (Box 72)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Center, Incorporated. (Box 72)
    - Projects. (Box 72)
    - Projects, E. 60th St. Youth Center. (Box 72)
    - Projects, Martin Luther King Hospital. (Box 72)
    - Public Relations (3). (Box 72)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 72)
    - Referrals (4). (Box 72)
    - Requests. (Box 73)
    - Schools, 29th District. (Box 73)
    - Schools, Miscellaneous. (Box 73)
    - Staff. (Box 73)
    - State Democratic Committee. (Box 73)
    - SubCommittee on Equal Opportunities. (Box 73)
    - Telegrams. (Box 73)
    - Thank You. (Box 73)
  - Subject Files, 1977
    - Public Relations, January-April [1977]. (Box 73)
    - Central City Mental Health. (Box 50)
    - Greater Los Angeles Community Action Agency. (Box 50)
    - Hawkins Family Foundation. (Box 50)
    - Huntington Park Office. (Box 50)
    - IMPAC, [South Central] Improvement Action Council. (Box 50)
    - Invitations, Hawkins. (Box 50)
    - Invitations, Knox. (Box 50)
    - Knox, Personal. (Box 50)
    - Legislation (2). (Box 50)
    - Mailing Lists. (Box 50)
      - Women's Organizations, Huntington Park and South Gate. (Box 50)
      - Attorneys, South Gate, Huntington Park, and Cudahy. (Box 50)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 50)
    - Neighborhood Adult Participation Project, South Central Manpower Training Center. (Box 50)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Center, Incorporated. (Box 50)
    - Political. (Box 50)
    - Projects. (Box 50)
    - Projects, Martin Luther King Hospital. (Box 50)
    - Public Relations (2). (Box 50)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 50)
    - Referral, (2)., January-June (Box 50)
    - Referral, (2)., July-December (Box 51)
    - Requests. (Box 51)
    - Schools Miscellaneous. (Box 51)
    - Staff. (Box 51)
    - State Democratic Committee. (Box 51)
    - SubCommittee on Employment Opportunities. (Box 51)
    - Telegrams. (Box 51)
    - Thank You. (Box 51)
  - Subject Files, 1979
    - Black Caucus. (Box 51)
    - Central City Mental Health. (Box 51)
    - County Democratic Central Committee. (Box 51)
    - Fund Raiser. (Box 51)
    - Greater Los Angeles Community Action Agency. (Box 51)
    - Huntington Park Office. (Box 51)
    - IMPAC, (South Central] Improvement Action Council. (Box 51)
    - Invitations, Hawkins. (Box 51)
    - Invitations, Knox. (Box 51)
    - Knox, Personal Legislation (2). (Box 51)
    - Mailing List. (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous Neighborhood Adult Participation Project, South Central Manpower Training Center. (Box 51)
    - Patron Mailing. (Box 51)
    - Political. (Box 51)
    - Projects. (Box 51)
    - Public Relations (4). (Box 51)
    - Recommendations, January-June. (Box 51)
    - Recommendations, July-December. (Box 52)
    - Referrals (4). (Box 52)
    - Public Relations, November-December. (Box 52)
    - Requests. (Box 52)
    - Schools, 29th District. (Box 52)
    - Schools, Miscellaneous. (Box 52)
    - Staff. (Box 52)
    - State Democratic Committee. (Box 52)
    - SubCommittee on Employment Opportunity. (Box 52)
    - Thank You. (Box 52)
    - Telegrams. (Box 52)
  - Subject Files, 1980
    - Black Caucus. (Box 52)
    - Central City Mental Health. (Box 52)
    - Coordinating Committee, 29th District. (Box 52)
    - County Democratic Central Committee. (Box 52)
    - Charles Drew Post Medical School. (Box 52)
    - Fact Sheet, 29th District. (Box 52)
    - Gilbert Lindsay Village Green Project. (Box 52)
    - Goodyear Rubber Company. (Box 52)
    - Huntington Park Office. (Box 52)
    - IMPAC, (South Central] Improvement Action Council. (Box 52)
    - Invitations, Hawkins. (Box 52)
    - Invitations, Knox. (Box 52)
    - Knox, Personal. (Box 52)
    - Legislation (2). (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 52)
    - Neighborhood Adult Participation Project, South Central Manpower Training Center. (Box 52)
    - Patron Mailing. (Box 52)
    - Political. (Box 52)
    - Projects. (Box 52)
    - Public Relations, January-February. (Box 52)
    - Public Relations, (5)., March-December (Box 53)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 53)
    - Referrals (4). (Box 53)
    - Requests. (Box 53)
    - Schools, 29th District. (Box 53)
    - Schools, Miscellaneous. (Box 53)
    - Senior Citizens. (Box 53)
    - Senior Citizens Programs in the 29th District. (Box 53)
    - SubCommittee on Employment Opportunities. (Box 53)
    - Staff. (Box 53)
    - Thank You. (Box 53)
    - Telegrams. (Box 53)
    - Trade Readjustment Allowance, Plant Closure. (Box 53)
  - Subject Files, 1981
    - Agencies List, 29th District Black Caucus. (Box 53)
    - Cases Referred to Washington, D.C. (Box 53)
    - Council of Baptist Ministers Meeting, December 1980. (Box 53)
    - Computer List Entry. (Box 53)
    - County Democratic Central Committee. (Box 53)
    - Congressional Record, Extension of Remarks. (Box 53)
    - Gilbert Lindsay Village Green Project. (Box 53)
    - Housing Authority of the County of Los Angeles. (Box 53)
    - Huntington Park Office. (Box 53)
    - Invitations, Hawkins. (Box 53)
    - Invitations, Knox. (Box 53)
    - Knox, Personal. (Box 53)
    - Legislation. (Box 53)
    - Legislation, H.R. 3824, Urban Enterprise Zone Bill. (Box 53)
    - Mailing List. (Box 53)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 53)
    - Neighborhood Adult Participation Project, South Central Manpower Training Center. (Box 53)
    - Operation Reach Out. (Box 53)
    - Patron Mailing. (Box 53)
    - Political. (Box 53)
    - Projects. (Box 53)
    - Public Relations (6). (Box 53)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 54)
    - Referrals (4). (Box 54)
    - Requests. (Box 54)
    - Schools, 29th District. (Box 54)
    - Senior Citizen Programs, 29th District. (Box 54)
    - Senior Citizen Intern Information. (Box 54)
    - Staff. (Box 54)
    - Thank You. (Box 54)
    - Technical Health Careers School, Incorporated. (Box 54)
    - Telegrams. (Box 54)
    - Transportation. (Box 54)
  - Subject Files, 1983
    - Ads Purchased for AFH. (Box 54)
    - Black Caucus. (Box 54)
    - Invitations (6). (Box 54)
    - Legislation. (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 54)
    - Neighborhood Adult Participation Project, South Central Manpower Training Center. (Box 54)
    - Public Relations (6). (Box 54)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 54)
    - Referrals (4). (Box 54)
    - Requests. (Box 54)
    - Senior Citizen Intern, Helen Niersbach. (Box 54)
    - Senior Citizen Intern Report, Tommye J. Moore. (Box 54)
    - Schools, Miscellaneous. (Box 54)
    - Small Business Workshop, July 1983. (Box 54)
    - Staff. (Box 54)
    - State Democratic Committee. (Box 54)
    - Telegrams. (Box 54)
    - Thank You. (Box 54)
  - Subject Files, 1984
    - Black Caucus. (Box 54)
    - Computer Letters. (Box 54)
    - Invitations. (Box 54)
    - Consolidated Veterans Administration Case. (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 54)
    - Patron Mailing. (Box 54)
    - Political. (Box 54)
    - Public Relations (6). (Box 55)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 55)
    - Referrals (4). (Box 55)
    - Requests. (Box 55)
    - Senior Citizens Referral Agencies. (Box 55)
    - Schools, Miscellaneous. (Box 55)
    - Speech, Congressman Hawkins, November 1984. (Box 55)
    - State Democratic Committee. (Box 55)
    - Thank You. (Box 55)
  - Subject Files, 1985
    - Community Meeting Information. (Box 55)
    - County Central Democratic Committee. (Box 55)
    - Invitations, Hawkins. (Box 55)
    - Legislation, July-December. (Box 55)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 55)
    - Public Relations (5). (Box 55)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 55)
    - Referrals (5). (Box 55)
    - Requests. (Box 55)
    - Senior Citizen Intern. (Box 55)
    - South Gate. (Box 55)
    - Staff. (Box 55)
    - Thank You. (Box 55)
    - W. (Box 55)
  - Subject Files, 1986
    - Invitations. (Box 55)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 55)
    - Public Relations (6). (Box 55)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 55)
    - Referrals (2). (Box 55)
    - Requests. (Box 55)
    - Staff. (Box 55)
  - Subject Files, 1987
    - Cases. (Box 55)
    - G. (Box 55)
    - H. (Box 55)
    - Invitations. (Box 55)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 55)
    - Political. (Box 55)
    - Projects. (Box 55)
    - Public Relations (6). (Box 55)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 55)
    - Referrals, (2)., January-June (Box 55)
    - Requests. (Box 55)
    - Staff. (Box 55)
  - Subject Files, 1988
    - Black Caucus. (Box 56)
    - Cases. (Box 56)
    - Invitations. (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 56)
    - Projects. (Box 56)
    - Public Relations (6). (Box 56)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 56)
    - Referrals (4). (Box 56)
    - Requests. (Box 56)
    - Staff. (Box 56)
    - Telegrams. (Box 56)
    - Thank Yous. (Box 56)
  - Subject Files, 1989
    - American Immigration Control Foundation. (Box 56)
    - FAX Transmissions. (Box 56)
    - Invitations. (Box 56)
    - Personal. (Box 56)
    - Public Relations (4). (Box 56)
    - Recommendations (2). (Box 56)
    - Referrals, January-June. (Box 56)
    - Requests (2). (Box 56)
    - Staff. (Box 56)
  - Washington File, 1972
    - Agencies. (Box 56)
    - Academy. (Box 56)
    - Administrative. (Box 56)
    - Campaign Cases (2). (Box 56)
    - Democratic National Committee. (Box 56)
    - Education. (Box 56)
    - Executive Departments. (Box 56)
    - Full Employment Task Force. (Box 56)
    - General. (Box 56)
    - Hearings. (Box 56)
    - Invitations. (Box 56)
    - Legislative. (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 56)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity. (Box 56)
    - Personal. (Box 56)
    - Political. (Box 56)
    - Projects. (Box 56)
    - Recommendations. (Box 56)
    - Referrals. (Box 56)
    - Requests. (Box 56)
    - Social Security. (Box 56)
  - Washington File, 1973
    - Academy. (Box 56)
    - Administrative. (Box 56)
    - Agencies. (Box 56)
    - Black Caucus. (Box 56)
    - Brownsville Raid. (Box 56)
    - Cases (2). (Box 57)
    - Executive. (Box 57)
    - General. (Box 57)
    - Invitations. (Box 57)
    - Legislation. (Box 57)
    - Nixon's Legislation. (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 57)
    - Personal. (Box 57)
    - Political. (Box 57)
    - Projects. (Box 57)
    - Recommendations. (Box 57)
    - Referrals. (Box 57)
    - Requests. (Box 57)
    - Social Security. (Box 57)
    - State Democratic Central Committee. (Box 57)
    - SubCommittee. (Box 57)
    - Telegrams. (Box 57)
    - Training Programs. (Box 57)
    - White House. (Box 57)
  - Washington File, 1977
    - Academy. (Box 57)
    - Administrative. (Box 57)
    - Agencies. (Box 57)
    - Black Caucus. (Box 57)
    - Cases (2). (Box 57)
    - Executive. (Box 57)
    - General. (Box 57)
    - Invitations. (Box 57)
    - Legislative. (Box 57)
    - Personal. (Box 57)
    - Political. (Box 57)
    - Projects. (Box 57)
    - Recommendations. (Box 57)
    - Referrals. (Box 57)
    - Requests. (Box 57)
    - Social Security. (Box 57)
    - State Democratic Central Committee. (Box 57)
    - SubCommittee. (Box 57)
    - Telegrams. (Box 57)
    - White House. (Box 57)
  - Washington File, 1978
    - Academy. (Box 57)
    - Administrative. (Box 57)
    - Agencies. (Box 57)
    - Black Caucus. (Box 57)
    - Cases (2). (Box 57)
    - General. (Box 57)
    - Executive. (Box 57)
    - Invitations. (Box 57)
    - Legislative. (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 57)
    - Personal. (Box 57)
    - Projects. (Box 57)
    - Recommendations. (Box 57)
    - Referrals. (Box 57)
    - Requests. (Box 57)
    - Telegrams. (Box 57)
    - Training Programs. (Box 57)
    - White House. (Box 57)
  - Washington File, 1979
    - Academy. (Box 58)
    - Agencies. (Box 58)
    - Black Caucus. (Box 58)
    - Cases (2). (Box 58)
    - Computer Letters. (Box 58)
    - Executive. (Box 58)
    - General. (Box 58)
    - Invitations. (Box 58)
    - Legislative. (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 58)
    - Personal. (Box 58)
    - Projects. (Box 58)
    - Recommendations. (Box 58)
    - Referrals. (Box 58)
    - Requests. (Box 58)
    - SubCommittee. (Box 58)
    - Telegrams. (Box 58)
    - Training Programs. (Box 58)
    - White House. (Box 58)
  - Washington File, 1980
    - Academy. (Box 58)
    - Administrative. (Box 58)
    - Agencies. (Box 58)
    - Black Caucus. (Box 58)
    - Cases (2). (Box 58)
    - Computer Letters. (Box 58)
    - Executive. (Box 58)
    - General. (Box 58)
    - Invitations. (Box 58)
    - Legislative. (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 58)
    - Personal. (Box 58)
    - Projects. (Box 58)
    - Recommendations. (Box 58)
    - Referrals. (Box 58)
    - Requests. (Box 58)
    - SubCommittee. (Box 58)
    - Telegrams. (Box 58)
    - Training Programs. (Box 58)
    - White House. (Box 58)
  - Washington File, 1981
    - Academy. (Box 58)
    - Administrative. (Box 58)
    - Agencies. (Box 58)
    - Black Caucus. (Box 58)
    - Cases (2). (Box 58)
    - Computer Letters. (Box 58)
    - Executive. (Box 58)
    - General. (Box 58)
    - Invitations. (Box 58)
    - Legislative. (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 58)
    - Personal. (Box 58)
    - Political. (Box 58)
    - Projects. (Box 58)
    - Recommendations. (Box 58)
    - Referrals. (Box 58)
    - Requests. (Box 58)
    - Social Security. (Box 58)
    - SubCommittee. (Box 58)
    - Telegrams. (Box 58)
    - Training Programs. (Box 58)
    - White House. (Box 58)
  - Washington File, 1982
    - Agencies. (Box 58)
    - Black Caucus. (Box 58)
    - Cases (2). (Box 58)
    - Executive. (Box 58)
    - General. (Box 59)
    - Invitations. (Box 59)
    - Legislative. (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 59)
    - Personal. (Box 59)
    - Political. (Box 59)
    - Recommendations. (Box 59)
    - Referrals. (Box 59)
    - Requests. (Box 59)
    - SubCommittee. (Box 59)
    - Telegrams. (Box 59)
    - White House. (Box 59)
  - Washington File, 1983
    - Agencies. (Box 59)
    - Black Caucus. (Box 59)
    - Cases (2). (Box 59)
    - Executive. (Box 59)
    - General. (Box 59)
    - Invitations. (Box 59)
    - Legislative. (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 59)
    - Personal. (Box 59)
    - Recommendations. (Box 59)
    - Referrals. (Box 59)
    - Requests. (Box 59)
    - SubCommittee. (Box 59)
    - Telegrams. (Box 59)
  - Washington File, 1984
    - Cases, A-L. (Box 59)
    - General. (Box 59)
    - Requests. (Box 59)
  - Washington File, 1984-85
    - A-Z. (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 59)
  - Washington File,, A-Z, 1986
  - Washington File,, A-Z, 1986-87
  - Washington File, 1988
    - January-June. (Box 59)
    - July-December. (Box 59)
  - Correspondence Logs, (13), 1983-89
  - Press Files
    - 1963
      - Biography, AFH. (Box 68)
      - Press Releases. (Box 68)
      - Newsletters. (Box 68)
      - Newsletters. (Box 68)
        - Economic Development Area, March (Box 68)
        - Report to Constituents, August. (Box 68)
        - Let's Win Civil Rights in, October., 1963 (Box 68)
        - Congress on the Move, October. (Box 68)
        - Where We Stand in Civil Rights, November. (Box 68)
        - Older Americans Act, November. (Box 68)
        - Apprenticeship Jobs, November. (Box 68)
        - The Passing of a President, November. (Box 68)
        - A Memorable Year, December. (Box 68)
    - , Public Relations, Radio and TV., 1963-66 (Box 68)
    - , Public Relations, Speeches., 1963-68 (Box 68)
      - Speech on African Americans, 1966-01-20 (Box 68)
      - Speech, the economic and social conditions of African Americans, 1966 (Box 68)
      - Remarks, President Kennedy's legislative program on civil rights: it's signifigance for the West, Western States Democratic Conference, 1962-09-20 (Box 68)
      - Speech, before the Senate Subcommittee on Manpower and Poverty, Los Angeles, California, 1967-05-12 (Box 68)
    - 1964
      - Press Releases (2). (Box 68)
      - Newsletters
        - Voter Registration, February. (Box 68)
        - After Civil Rights, What?, February. (Box 68)